Hello, welcome to the next episode of Learn German in Hindi.
Today we are going to
learn a very interesting work.
Now, this word Larson is used a lot
in today's life or when we speak it, it is
used a lot outside and in a very good way. So, that is why
today we are going to learn some of its important uses. So
first of all, let's see how it works. It works
very
simply. You must also be seeing it on the screen.
This plaster two glass entry latch Veer
Wilson, it works very simply. Everyone understood
that it should be taken away from Islam. If we learn to use it, then
first of all we will use it as a
shield. It will remain
in the main section. So we use it.
Hey friend, we will get it done. Then we get
something done and get it done from someone else.
For example, I repair my car.
If I get it repaired from someone, from a mechanic, then
what will I say? Islam
's repair run. Okay, that's where I
wash my shirt. This year there is a guava. I get
my shirt repaired from someone.  If you get this lakh
white murder reading simple admission done then
what will you do with lakh injustice,
you will do model Nargis, member end is needed now the
second use of it is that many times
if you are in Germany then you will see that you call clutch as
laddu answer by late it is because of this it is of
Lakhan, it is of profit or lunch behind the back
licensed physician and then garlic
status ringtone is a
simple so it is like loot many times it is
strong and there is one more use of it people get
confused by it leave it
like limit last remedies 10 leave it friend
lakh sangeeta or else he cannot
quit cigarette arkan das Ravana nishtha lakshana
Chitrakoot smoking can das Ravana list
garlic in it like normal v now
going a little further it means leave Lakshmi people
then Allah leave me alone then mushroom
then let people live in peace all these are
used so this is me and some of its
types
so like it and I will tell you just after
that Allah do it in this way also
I will give birth to my daughter on Sunday  Let me watch TV,
okay, I love island, every watch TV on Sunday,
so what about Islam, main doctor, common
zonetag parents, burning alerts, all these
news channels, those natives who have come out,
their mother tongue, so what were these
four important for us, first of all let's get
this Lakshya done, Manav to Tripurari
Sharan, second that let's do it, I have liked it,
third liquid garlic won and fourth
general admission rule, I hope you all
understood this confirmation, we will meet
in the next episode, thank you